(Mrs Cooper:)Anyway, when he went on the Internet
to get some...
(Mrs Cooper:)...a man from the government came by
and sat him down real gentle...
(Mrs Cooper:)...and told him it's against the law
to have yellow cake uranium in a shed.
- Well, what happened?
- Well, poor boy had a fit.
(Mrs Cooper:)Locked himself in his room
and built a sonic death ray.
- A death ray?
- Well, that's what he called it.
Didn't even slow down the neighbor kids.
Heh.
(Mrs Cooper:)It pissed our dog off to no end.
(Mrs Cooper:)You know, you two make a cute couple.
[BOTH LAUGH]
I... No, no.
No, we're not a couple. We're singles.
(Leonard:)Two singles. Like those individually
wrapped slices of cheese that...
Or friends.
- Did I pluck a nerve there?
- Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)Okay.
All right, everybody, it's time to eat.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, Lord, we thank you for this meal
and for all your bounty.
(Mrs Cooper:)And we pray that you help Sheldon
get back on his rocker.